https://home.privateerpress.com/terms-of-service/

Terms of Service
By posting, uploading, inputting, providing, or submitting (“Posting”) in or on any of our services, you are granting Privateer permission to use your Posting in connection with the operation of our business (including, without limitation, all Privateer publications), including, without limitation, the license rights to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate, and reformat your Posting; to publish your name in connection with your Posting. No compensation will be paid with respect to the use of your Posting, as provided herein. Privateer is under no obligation to post or use any Posting you may provide.
By Posting, you warrant and represent that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to your Posting including, without limitation, all the rights necessary for you to provide, post, upload, input, or submit the Posting. In addition to the warranty and representation set forth above, by Posting anything that contain images, photographs, pictures, or that are otherwise graphical in whole or in part (“Images”), you warrant and represent that (a) you are the copyright owner of such Images, or that the copyright owner of such Images has granted you permission to use such Images or any content and/or images contained in such Images consistent with the manner and purpose of your use and as otherwise permitted by these Services, (b) you have the rights necessary to grant the licenses and sublicenses described herein, and (c) that each person depicted in such Images, if any, has provided consent to the use of the Images as set forth herein, including, by way of example, and not as a limitation, the distribution, public display and reproduction of such Images. By Posting Images, you are granting (a) to all members of the general public permission to use your Images in connection with the use of any of the Services, including, though not limited to, making prints and gift items which include such Images, and including, without limitation, a non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free license to: copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, translate, and reformat your Images without having your name attached to such Images, and the right to sublicense such rights to any supplier of the Services. The licenses granted in the preceding sentences for any Images will terminate at the time you completely remove such Images from the Services, provided that such termination shall not affect any licenses granted in connection with such Images prior to the time you completely remove such Images. Privateer does not claim any ownership of the aforementioned Postings and Images in any case.
Claims of Copyright Infringement
All claims of copyright infringement should be made to Frontdesk@privateerpress.com
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
PRIVATEER PROVIDES ITS WEBSITES TO YOU “AS-IS,” WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, CORRECTNESS, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. PRIVATEER DOES NOT WARRANT THAT OUR WEBSITES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS OR ACHIEVE A PARTICULAR RESULT OR THAT YOUR USE OF THESE WEBSITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT THESE WEBSITES OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKES THEM AVAILABLE ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. IF YOUR VISITATION OF THESE WEBSITES OR THE USE OF MATERIAL CONTAINED ON THESE WEBSITES RESULTS IN YOUR NEED TO SERVICE OR REPLACE ANY PROPERTY, MATERIAL, EQUIPMENT, DATA, OR OTHER ITEM, THEN PRIVATEER SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR THOSE COSTS. WITHOUT LIMITING THE GENERALITY OF THE FOREGOING SENTENCES, PRIVATEER SHALL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, INDIRECT, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF YOUR USE OF THESE WEBSITES. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITES IS AN IMPLICIT AGREEMENT TO ALL THE TERMS LISTED HEREIN AND A MATERIAL PORTION OF OUR AGREEMENT TO PROVIDE THESE WEBSITES TO YOU. IN THE EVENT THAT YOU MADE A PURCHASE FROM THESE WEBSITES, PRIVATEER’S TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FROM ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES, AND CAUSES OF ACTION SHALL NEVER EXCEED THE AMOUNT YOU PAID TO PRIVATEER. DESPITE WHATEVER CONTRACTS OR AGREEMENTS ARE WRITTEN TO THE CONTRARY BETWEEN YOU AND PRIVATEER, THIS CLAUSE SHALL REMAIN CONTROLLING, OVERRIDING, AND IN EFFECT.
Privacy Policy
Privateer Press, Incorporated (hereinafter known as Privateer), takes the protection of your personal information very seriously while you are visiting our websites. We do not collect and keep any personal information online from you unless you volunteer it and you are 13 years of age or older. We also do not collect and keep personal information online from children under the age of 13 without consent of a parent or legal guardian, except in limited circumstances authorized by law.
Privateer Press strictly adheres to the policies created by the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. No information will be collected for anyone under the age of 13 without parental consent. Children may need to enter a user name and password in order to access some portions of the site, but they will never be required to enter their personal information. Children in ongoing customer service relations with Privateer Press may be required to supply their personal information for solutions to their customer service issues. This information will only be retained for the duration required to reach a conclusion with the customer service issue, at which time the personal information will be destroyed.
All personal information obtained will only be distributed to other third parties in cases where it will improve customer service or where such information is required to complete transactions made on the website. Information collected from you will be used to enhance your experience with the website(s) or allow you to make purchases from the website(s).
For our full privacy policy, please visit https://store.privateerpress.com/privacypolicy
Cookies
Privateer Press will utilize cookies in order to enhance and personalize your experience with our website(s). Cookies generated from exploring our website(s) will never contain your personal information unless you have willfully given it to us as a part of interacting with the website(s).
Menu
